hey guys rexin here welcome to another
crash course guide for Aang Yao for a
super crash course version of this
simply spam e skill while spamming basic
attack like this and spamming e skill
whenever you're ready even during his
ultimate press ultimate and keep
spamming both buttons e skill and basic
attack there are no repercussions to
this except for maybe a broken
controller or a mouse but that is how
you correctly play him there is no way
to go wrong in this otherwise if you
want to learn more about how his skill
Works continue watching or skip to this
part of the video
[Music]
he is really simple to play as you can
see at the bottom here on his Forte
gauge there's a gauge and all you need
to do is press e your resonance skill
once it's full and he gains his gauge
based on simply attacking the enemy like
this and once it's full you will hear a
beep and his e skill will be glowing
simply press e and press basic attack
right after it and this will
happen so in short whenever the gauge is
full press e and basic attack because he
will Lodge the enemy and follow up with
a air combo now when the gauge is not
full his e attack will look like this it
will also gr Forte gauge and the good
news is that the non full Forte gauge e
skill shares a different internal
cooldown as the full gauge one so I'll
show you what I mean so look over here
it's almost full I'll use my e skill and
look it's still available to press when
it's full and then you you see here so
it shares a separate internal cooldown
so in summary always spam your e skill
whenever it's ready it's free damage
basically so pretty much you will do
this when you're charging the gauge
whenever e is ready just press e and
then spam
basic and then it's full press e air
press e again spam
basic press e basic press e again basic
you get the idea whenever e is ready
just press it outside of that keep
spamming basic that's how you play sang
Yao it's really simple so let's talk
about his resonance Liberation when he
pops his ultimate his Forte gauge will
be split into five segments and this
five segments will be filled simply by
doing three basic attacks or Dodge
counter or pressing e and basic attack
so we'll just do the basics three basic
attack each for sang Yao he can do three
hyper cubes hyper Cube refers to
pressing E when the gauge is full so let
me show you I'll press
ultimate now three basic attack 1 2 3
it's full press e that's one hyper Cube
do it again three basic
attack press
e and again three basic
e so that's the most basic form of his
ultimate now let's talk about the
optimal input during his ultimate so
remember when your gauge is full during
normal form and then you press e and
basic attack he does this air
combo like
this so whenever he does e during his
ultimate plus basic attack he does the
exact same thing except it also gives
him a full gauge right away so in short
during his ultimate for the first hyper
Cube all you need to do is press e and
basic attack and the gauge will be full
and then you press e again and then
while that e is on cool down the for the
second hyper Cube just do three basic
attack and then press e again and for
the third hyper Cube the cool down
should be finished and then you can
press e plus basic attack and then press
e again so that sounds like a mouthful
I'll go through step by step during his
ultimate for the first hyper Cube press
e and basic attack and then e so first
hyper
Cube e basic attack air combo see how
it's full press e that's the first hyper
Cube and then look down here so this is
on cool down so for that during that
cool down just do three basic
attack and then E for for the second
hyper Cube and now that the cool down is
back up you do the same again e basic
attack air
combo and finish it off with
e so in short three hyper cubes first
and third hyper cube is just e basic
attack for the second hyper Cube just do
three basic attacks and that's pretty
much it for sang Yao it's all about
clicking basic attack and spamming your
e pretty much you don't even need to use
your brain for this like as long as e is
ready just press e e basic attack spam
and then you can pretty much just press
both button at once like e and basic
attack together like
this same for ultimate once ultimate is
ready e basic attack straight
away e basic attack e three basic
attack and then e basic attack
again and that's it that's for sangao
very simple very brain dead as for his
weapon Verity's handle is his main
weapon so this has the most damage
followed by Abyss surges if you have
this already otherwise any fourst star
weapon with damage output also works for
him as for his Echoes you can go Tempest
mephis or thundering mephis I personally
like Tempest meis because the echo is
way faster to activate and then you can
go 4 3311 on these and for the three
cost Electro damage or attack percent
you can also go for 4111 cost with both
mephis and both of them going crit or
crit damage depending if you have his
sign weapon or not because his signature
weapon has crit rate and then if you're
feeling lucky you can just roll crit
rate on all pieces and then just go
double crit damage on both pieces of the
for cost now with Electro set aside
Sanga can also go lingering Tunes me
Abomination is really good Echo because
it's a summon Echo so it doesn't take up
animation time from your attacks and
also it massively improves outro skill
damage by 60% since Yang Yao is the main
DPS and his outro skill is pure damage
for the lingering tune set it's the
typical 43311 configuration with crit
damage or crit rate depending on the
main weapon you're holding now let's
look at his skills all you need to know
here is his Forte circuit and resonance
Liberation simply prioritize all your
points into resonance Liberation and
Forte circuit the two inherent skills
and that's it the rest can stay at
around level six and intro skill is not
that important you can keep it at level
one or level six depending on your
resources and as you can see over here
his outro skill like I said before it's
pure damage this is why lingering Tunes
is a good consideration for him as for
his resonance chain it's all pure damage
All Pure damage increase as for the
fourth chain it's a resonance Liberation
buff for the entire team after casting
his own and for the fifth chain his
damage multiplier of his Ultra skill is
increased by 222% so when you're this
far in the resonance chain lingering
Tunes Echo is a really good
consideration and S6 is just even more
damage so that's pretty much it for sang
Yao he's already very much playable at
s0 as you saw in the demonstration
earlier so more resonance chain
obviously means more damage team
composition wise overwork Vina always on
the first rotation followed by Yin Lin
or Changi if you have her since both of
them buff resonance Liberation jinen
also works as well since jinen improved
resonance Liberation by 38% apart from
that anyone pretty much goes for the
second rotation as long as sangao is on
the third rotation since his is pure
damage so you want him to be the last on
the team rotation but yeah that's pretty
much it for sang Yao's crash course I
hope this guy has been helpful to you in
understanding his gam play and how to
set him up consider leaving a like
comment and subscribe to the channel and
I'll see you in the next video bye-bye